为什么这年代了召唤蝙蝠侠还用蝙蝠信号灯
But why do they still call Batman using the Bat-Signal?
直接发条短信请他来不是更方便吗
Wouldn't it just be, like, easier to text him?
蝙蝠信号灯不只是用来召唤蝙蝠侠
The Bat-Signal isn't just to alert Batman,
还有震慑他敌人内心的功用
it's also to strike fear in the hearts of his enemies
让他们知道蝙蝠侠要来了
and let them know he's coming.
就像谢尔顿的三段敲门法
Sort of like Sheldon's knock.
嘲讽我跟蝙蝠侠类似吗  我接受
Comparing me to Batman? I'll take it.
如果我们不出手
If we don't do anything,
你们觉得他们能聊多久的蝙蝠侠
how long do you think they'll talk about Batman?
我认识他们已经有11年了  所以...
Well, I've know them for 11 years, so...
11年吧
11 years.
我觉得他们也有给他发短信
I believe they do text him.
蝙蝠信号灯通过蓝牙连到他手机
The-the Bat-Signal is linked to his phone via Bluetooth.
漫画里有画过吗
Has that been in the comics?
没  我个人这么认为而已
No, it's just what I believe.
够了  我要让他们停下
All right, I'm putting a stop to this.
你如果知道办法  你为什么还等了11年啊
If you knew how, why'd you wait 11 years?
各位  告诉你们
Hey, guys, guess what?
我今天上班发现我要跟比尔·盖茨见面了
Today at work, I found out I am going to meet Bill Gates.
抱歉  莱纳德  你跟佩妮的缘分到此为止了
Sorry, Leonard, you and Penny had a good run.
你确定吗  我猜他家的网应该超快呢
You sure? I-I bet his Internet's really fast.
你怎么会有此荣幸
How did this happen?
他的慈善基金会在寻找
Well, his foundation is looking to partner
我不会为了比尔·盖茨而甩了他
I'm not leaving him for Bill Gates.
制药公司来合作研发价格低廉的疫苗
with a pharmaceutical company to help develop affordable vaccines
所以公司让我带他转转
so they asked me to show him around.
太好了  他什么时候来
That's great. When's he coming?
他大概周日  周一早晨到
Uh, he gets in on Sunday, and Monday morning,
我会带他去看看实验室和办公区域
I'm gonna give him a tour of the labs and offices.
他周日  也就是4月1号到吗
Oh. He gets in on Sunday, April first?
想得美  佩妮
Nice try, Penny.
你在说什么
What're you talking about?
4月1日愚人节
April Fools' Day.
想必这又是另一个你年年
This is another one of your classic pranks
想愚弄我的恶作剧之一吧
you try to pull on me every year.
我从来没有对你恶作剧过啊
Literally never pulled a prank on you.
是吗  那去年
Oh, really? What about last year,
你给我发一封电邮写了照片请见附件
when you sent me that e-mail with the photo attached,
结果根本没附件
but you didn't attach a photo.
那是我犯错了
That was a mistake.
想耍我  你当然是犯了错
Messing with me? Yes, it was.
所以今年
And this year,
我不会再上你的当
I am not falling for it.
-谢尔顿  我发誓...  -别  你这是在干嘛
- Sheldon, I swear... - No... what are you doing?
被你猜中了  他没有要来  愚人节
Oh, you're right. He's not coming. April fools.
常言道
You know what they say,
耍我"N"次
fool me "N" Times,
"N"等于你已经耍到我的次数
where "N" equals the amount of times you've already fooled me,
你傻逼
shame on you.
耍我"N+1"次  我傻逼
Fool me "N" plus one times, shame on me.
第十一季  第十八集
所以你要跟比尔·盖茨共处一天
So you're gonna spend a day with Bill Gates.
我有点小嫉妒啊
I'm a little jealous.
我还有点小紧张呢
Well, I'm a little nervous.
如果我这次做得好  我希望公司能考虑一下
You know, if I do a good job, I'm hoping they'll consider me
最近刚空出来的公关职位
for a PR position that's opening up.
如果你很紧张  我知道很多关于他的事
Well, if you're nervous, I-I know a lot about him.
我可以帮你补习  或者陪你一起  我都行
I can fill you in or maybe come along, whatever.
我觉得我没事的
I think I'll be okay.
我举个例子  万一他想要
Well, I'm-I'm just saying, what are you gonna do
跟你聊微型计算机的
when he wants to talk about high-level language interpreters
高级语言翻译程序怎么办
for microcomputers?
什么是微型计算机的高级语言翻译程序啊
What are high-level language interpreters for microcomputers?
一种为电脑编程的方式
A way of programming computers
是用语言与指令而不是用二进制代码
using words and commands instead of binary code.
这还挺有意思的呢  再跟我说说
Oh. That's actually kind of interesting. Tell me more.
其实嘛...
Oh, well...
这样  我会用这招回他
That, I'll do that. Mm-hmm.
-我真是完全没料到啊  -是啊
- I didn't even see it coming. - Yeah, well...
你从来都没料到过
You never do.
只是...  只是他是我的一个偶像
Well, I-it's just, he's an idol of mine
我真的很想有机会跟他见见面
and I would love the chance to hang out with him.
我知道你想见他
Look, I know you want to meet him,
但我不能把这事变成社交活动  好吗
but I can't turn this into a social thing, okay?
这是我的工作  我得确保这事办得妥当
This is my job. I really need it to go well.
懂  我懂  你说得对
I get it, I get it. You're right.
其实  其实我以前已经见过他一次了啦
Actually, I've-I've already met him once before.
他在普林斯顿大学演讲  我妈带我去了
He gave a talk at Princeton and my mom took me.
真的吗  他人好相处吗
Oh, really? Was he nice?
人超好
He's super nice.
后来我太激动就开始哭了什么的...
I-I got pretty emotional and started crying and...
他也没有取笑我什么的
He didn't make fun of me or anything.
你当时只是个孩子嘛
Well, you were a kid.
嗯哼
Uh-huh.
再见了  孩子们  我爱你们
Bye, my babies, I love you.
妈咪  我们也爱你
We love you, too, Mommy.
下次不许再恶心我
Yeah, don't do that.
伯纳黛特
Bernadette?
-你们要去哪里  -公园[西语]
- Hi. Where you off to? - El parque.
公园[西语]吗
El parque?
我在学西语  这样才能跟其他保姆聊天
I'm learning Spanish so I can talk to the other nannies.
学得如何
How's that going?
好[西语]
Bueno.
好啊
Good?
不  好[西语]
No bueno.
-谢谢你来陪我  -小事
- Thanks for coming over. - No problem.
想喝什么吗
Can I get you anything?
果汁  "蕉蕉"
Juice box? 'Naners?
什么是"蕉蕉"
'Naners?
抱歉  当妈的脑子
Sorry. Mom brain.
我都快忘了怎么跟成人说话了
I think I've forgot how to talk to grown-ups.
我是说香蕉蕉
I meant ba-naners.
没事啦  不用了
You know what, I'm good.
好吧
Okay.
我们看的这是什么
So, what are we watching?
《建筑师巴布》  我帮你补一下剧情
Bob the Builder. I'll catch you up.
这位就是巴布
That one's Bob.
他是个建筑师
He's a builder.
这不是儿童节目吗
Isn't this a kids show?
我们家里就看这个
It's what we watch in this house.
《建筑师巴布》《恐龙列车》
Bob the Builder, Dinosaur Train,
《小猪佩奇》  逗趣又意义深远
and Peppa Pig, which is both funny and meaningful.
你要不要休息一下  一起去吃点东西
You want to take a break and maybe get something to eat?
好啊
Sure.
怎么感觉不到有要出发的意思
Why does it not feel like we're going?
稍等  我看看巴布能不能修好
Hang on, I-I just want to see if Bob can fix it.
巴布的招牌台词  Yes, I / we can.
是的  他可以
Yes, he can!
你来啦
Oh, hey.
我替你折好了衣服  不用谢
I folded your laundry for you. You're welcome.
那不是我的啊
Uh, that's not mine.
你的意思是  这些不是你的
You're saying that these aren't yours?
不是
No.
所以你的意思是  我正摸着
So you're saying that I'm touching
陌生人的内裤
a stranger's underpants?
是的
Yes.
就这样  今天成了我人生最惨的一天
And just like that, it's the worst day of my life.
等等  你为什么要怪里怪气的
Wait, why are you being so weird?
因为我想到比尔·盖茨的事有可能是真的
It occurred to me that perhaps you were telling the truth about Bill Gates
而不是只是你精心铺垫的恶作剧一环
and it wasn't just part of an elaborate prank.
恶作剧的部分会是什么啊
What would the prank part even be?
我跑去见比尔·盖茨  尽管你说"不许来"
I show up to meet Bill Gates over your "objections,"
结果到场了才发现不是比尔·盖茨
but it's not Bill Gates at all, no.
是那种你聘请来派对的名人装扮者
It's one of those look-alikes that you hire for a party.
而当我手里拿着
And then when I go around
"比尔·盖茨"给我折的气球玩具
showing everybody the balloon animal
到处让别人看时  我就会像个智障
that "Bill Gates" made for me, I'll look like an idiot.
你是不是偷偷喝洗衣液了
Have you been eating laundry detergent?
我只是想要你告诉我实话
I just need you to tell me the truth.
我快被逼疯了
This is driving me crazy.
谢尔顿  他真的会来
Sheldon, he is really coming.
-真的吗  -真的
- Is he?  - He is.
-不骗我  -没骗你
- Really? - Yeah.
这下我不知道该相信啥了
Well, now I don't know what to believe!
谢谢你带我出来
Thanks for getting me out of the house.
我觉得我脑子都快变浆糊了
I feel like my brain is turning to mush.
我很乐意帮你
Happy to help.
我有没有给你看孩子们坐着的视频呀
Did I show you the video of the kids sitting?
有  你半夜3点发给我了
Yes, you texted it to me at 3:00 a.m.
还以为是谁被抓或者挂了呢
Thought someone was either in jail or dead.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
没事  至少让我在重新入睡时
No, no, I-it gave me something to watch
有令我想睡的东西看
while I tried to go back to sleep.
不行  我不要做那种
You know what? I don't want to be one of those moms
只会聊孩子的妈妈
who can only talk about her kids.
好吧  我正在读一本挺有趣的书
Okay, well, I'm reading a pretty good book.
关于文艺复兴时期鲜为人知的女艺术家
It's the untold story of female artists during the Renaissance.
我也在读书
Oh, I'm in the middle of a book, too.
它有三页长  可以飘在浴缸里
It's three pages long and floats in the bath.
我们也可以聊些其他的
All right, we can talk about something else.
你一挤那书  它就呱呱叫
It also quacks when you squeeze it.
迈克笑得可开心了  我这儿有视频
You should've seen Michael laugh. I think I have a video.
看来没法聊其他的了
Or maybe we can't.
好莱坞著名配乐家
你的网名怎么叫"约翰·威廉姆斯"
Why is your screen name "John Williams"?
因为哥永远在得分[配乐]
Uh, because I always score.
我要去一趟办公室
Hey, I think I'm gonna head to the office for a little bit.
-周日也去吗  -对呀
- On a Sunday? - Yeah.
我想为明天做好准备
Want to make sure I'm prepared for tomorrow.
你能让比尔·盖茨帮我
Do you think you could get Bill Gates
签个东西吗
to sign something for me?
好呀  签什么
Yeah, maybe, like what?
签我的手臂  我的胸膛  看他的意思吧
Oh, my arm, my chest, his call.
他只会有叫警察的意思
His call will be to the police.
佩妮  还记得我向你推荐
Penny, remember when I introduced you
只有100大卡的德芙巧克力条时
to 100 calorie Dove bars
你说你欠我一个大人情吗
and you said you owed me, like, big-time?
各位  就算我想要介绍你们
Guys, even if I wanted to introduce you,
他的时间表也已经排满了
there is no room in his schedule.
真的  看看这个行程
I mean, look. Look at this itinerary.
明天一早我和他在酒店碰面
I meet him at his hotel first thing tomorrow morning,
然后我们一整天都要到处跑
then we're on the go all day long.
你说得对  各位  这是她的工作
You're right. Guys, this is her job.
我们不要给她添麻烦
We need to respect that.
-谢了  宝贝  -为你骄傲哦
- Thank you, honey. - Proud of you.
爱你
Love you.
我刚才看到他下榻的酒店名字了
I totally just saw what hotel he's staying at.
那我们还等什么呢
What are we waiting here for?
等佩妮下完楼梯
For Penny to walk down the stairs,
上车离开啊
get in her car, and drive away.
对  真聪明
Right, smart.
-够了没  -她动作很快的  我们走
- Is that long enough? - She's pretty quick, let's go.
如果你有十亿美元  你要做什么
What would you do if you had a billion dollars?
和比尔·盖茨一样
Same as Bill Gates,
让世界变得更好一些
try to make the world a better place,
不过我要穿着功能完整的钢铁侠盔甲去做
but I'd do it in a working Iron Man suit.
我不知道那身盔甲还有男童中码
I didn't know that came in a boys' medium.
这是个馊主意
Th-This is a bad idea.
我们还是走吧
Maybe we should go.
-你在说什么呢  -我不知道
- What are you talking about? - I don't know.
我觉得很有罪恶感
I'm just feeling guilty,
就像我背着佩妮在搞鬼一样
like I'm kind of sneaking around behind Penny's back.
我们又没做错事
We're not doing anything wrong.
我们只是在一家酒店大厅闲逛
We're just hanging out in a hotel lobby.
好多人都这么做
Plenty of people do that:
商人啦  高级妓女呀
businessmen, high-end prostitutes.
这个新游戏很不错
That's a fun new game,
猜猜是执行长还是妓女
CEO or Ho.
这是不对的  我们还是走吧
No, this is wrong, let's go.
各位 各位  他来了
Guys, guys, that's him.
-冷静  -额滴神  额滴神
- Be cool. - Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
额滴神  额滴神
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
-再冷静点  -额滴神  额滴神
- Cooler. - Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
盖茨先生  我是莱纳德·霍夫斯塔德博士
Uh, M-Mr. Gates, I'm-I'm Dr. Leonard Hofstadter.
我们之前见过
We've actually met before.
抱歉  我不记得了
Sorry, I don't remember.
你人特别好  对我来说意义重大
You were so nice, a-and it was really special to me
因为你一直是我的人生偶像
because you've been such a big influence on my life.
在我还小的时候
I mean, ever since I was a little kid,
我就把你视为英雄
I've looked up to you like-like a hero.
现在我想起来了
Oh, now I remember.
你需要纸巾吗
Would you like a tissue?
给我一个拥抱如何
How about a hug?
还是来张纸巾吧
How-how about a tissue?
抱歉我一直把孩子挂在嘴边
Sorry I talked about my kids the whole time.
别担心
Oh, don't worry about it.
除了你帮我把肉都切成小块以外
I mean, besides you cutting up my meat for me,
午饭还是吃得挺开心
it was a lovely lunch.
天啊  这一切都是怎么了
God. What's happening?
我是个聪明  受过高等教育  成功的...
I'm a smart, educated, successful...
"女性"吗
"Woman"?
我只是卡壳了一下
I was gonna get it.
别对自己太苛刻了
Don't be so hard on yourself.
怀孕和生娃是真的会
Pregnancy and childbirth actually cause physical changes
改变你的大脑结构
to the structure of your brain.
我喜欢我原来的大脑结构
I liked the old structure of my brain.
不过话说回来  我喜欢我原来所有的结构
But then, I liked a lot of my old structures.
这些都是正面的改变
Well, these are positive changes.
对老鼠的研究表明  新妈妈对危险更敏感
Studies with rats show that new mothers
更善于同时处理多项任务
are more sensitive to danger, better at multitasking
寻找食物时也更大胆
and bolder in the pursuit of food.
我的确在皮包里塞了几块羊排
I did stick a couple lamp chops in my purse.
我说怎么有味道呢
So that's what I was smelling.
听着  就算你的大脑发生了变化
Look, even though your brain is different,
从很多方面来说  都是好的
in many ways, it's better.
可你不会无聊吗
But were you bored?
当然不会
Of course not.
你在撒谎
You're lying.
而你可以辨别  因为你的母性大脑
Which you can tell, because your maternal brain is better
对非语言的暗示更敏感了
at sensing nonverbal cues.
你现在就是在口蜜腹剑了
Now you're just being condescending.
看看你  两次都猜对了
Look at you, two for two.
留个门
Uh, hold the door.
Hold the door!
莱纳德
Oh. Hi, Leonard.
你没听到我喊留个门吗
Didn't you hear me yell "Hold the door"?
我听到了  但你知道大家怎么说的
I did. But you know what they say,
"多留个门  被闯空门"
"Hold the door, get robbed some more."
没有这种说法
No one says that.
那他们应该这么说
Oh. Well, they should,
因为这是真的  而且还押韵
because it's true, and it rhymes.
你去哪里了
So where have you been?
其实呢  我见到了比尔·盖茨
Actually, I met Bill Gates.
我明白了
I see.
你们都是一伙的
You're all in on it.
得了吧
Uh, nice try.
这不是愚人节玩笑  谢尔顿
It's not an April Fools' joke, Sheldon.
我真的去酒店见到了他
I actually went to a hotel and met him.
行行行
Right, right. Okay, so, uh,
"比尔·盖茨"就在"你去"的那家"酒店"里
"Bill Gates" was at the "Hotel" that you "went to."
为什么"去"也要加引号
Why is "went to" in quotes?
好吧
Fine.
"比尔·盖茨"就在你去的
So "Bill Gates" was at the "Hotel"
那家"酒店"里
that you went to.
这是你和比尔·盖茨
That's you and Bill Gates.
没错
It is.
-你这是哭了吗  -没有
- Were you crying? - No.
所以
So,
这不是玩笑  我本来真有机会见他
it wasn't a joke, and I actually could've met him?
他应该还在那儿呢
Well, he's probably still there.
哪间酒店
What hotel?
千橡市的拉昆塔酒店
The La Quinta Inn in Thousand Oaks,
入住名是赫尔南德斯
under the name Hernandez.
谢谢  太谢谢你了
Thank you, thank you so much!
愚人节快乐
April fools.
你到哪儿去了
Hey, where you been?
跟兄弟们一起玩
Uh, just hanging out with the guys.
他们还在生我的气吗
They still mad at me?
本来还在生气  但我说"嘿"
Uh, they were, but then I was like, "Hey,"
他们说"啥"  我又说"你们知道的"
and they were like, "What?" And I was like, "You know,"
他们就说"好吧"
and they were like, "Okay."
你真是个好丈夫
You're a good husband.
这不是我说了算的  但你这么说了
Well, it's not for me to say, but you just said it,
所以你应该是对的吧
so you're probably right.
原来
Well, as it turns out,
明晚有一个为盖茨先生办的接待会
there is a little reception for Mr. Gates tomorrow night.
我问能不能带上你  他们说可以
I asked if I could bring you, and they said yes.
什么
What?
你又可以和比尔·盖茨见面了
Yeah, you get to meet Bill Gates again.
等等  你说"又见面"是什么意思
Wait, what do you mean "again"?
因为你跟你妈之前见过他一次
'Cause you met him that one time with your mom.
没错
Yes.
然后明天又见一次
And then again tomorrow,
总共两次  只有这两次
for a total of two, and only two times.
对  不知道他记不记得你
Yeah. I wonder if he'll remember you.
我也想知道
Yeah, I wonder that, too.
太阳每秒
The sun is losing about
约减少6x10^12克
six times ten to the 12th grams per second,
所以太阳每年减少的质量百分比
so the fraction of the mass it loses every year
约为10^(-13)
is about ten to the negative 13th.
不过别担心哦
But don't worry.
还要几百万年后  我们才会通通冻死
It'll be millions of years before we all freeze to death.
做个好梦
Sweet dreams.
《在爸爸身上蹦来跳去》结尾突然阴暗啊
Hop on Pop took a dark turn there at the end.
艾米让我意识到刚生产完的妈妈
Amy made me realize that new mothers are cognitively primed
吸收新知识的能力是最强的  而我却浪费在
to take in new information, and I've been wasting it
瞎编关于我们宝宝脚趾的歌曲上
making up songs about our babies' toes.
说句公道话  《粉粉脚趾》我也参与写作了
To be fair, I cowrote "Pinky Toe, Pinky Toe."
进化论给了我妈妈大脑来专注于宝宝身上
Evolution gave me this mom brain to focus on the baby,
但我觉得可以用来学习各种新知识
but I figure I can hack it to learn all kinds of new things.
那好棒啊
Well, that's great.
没错  出了问题  我成功解决了
Yeah. There was a problem, and I fixed it.
就像《建筑师巴布》在长颈鹿笼子里那次一样
Like Bob the Builder in that giraffe cage.
不许剧透
Spoiler alert.
我还没看那集呢
I didn't see that one yet.
很开心啊
So that's fun.
你又能见到比尔·盖茨了
You get to meet Bill Gates again.
不开心  我死定了
It's not fun, I'm screwed.
我们看好戏看得很开心啊
It's fun for us. ?
也许他不记得你呢
Maybe he won't remember you.
我的鼻涕沾到他领带上了
I snotted on his tie.
没错  沾了超多啊
Yeah, you did, like, a lot.
你好  莱纳德
Hello, Leonard.
我想着你应该在这
Thought I'd find you here.
你这毒蛇
You snake.
怎么回事
What's going on?
距离约70多公里
他让我大老远跑去千橡市见比尔·盖茨
He sent me all the way to Thousand Oaks to meet Bill Gates
然而他很清楚人家根本不住在那
when he knew full well he wasn't staying there.
莱纳德  那太过分了
Wha-- Leonard, that's terrible.
是啊  你干嘛这样
Yeah, why would you do that?
距离约50多公里
你明知道他住在长滩市的希尔顿逸林酒店
You know he's staying at the DoubleTree in Long Beach.
等一下
Wait.
我怎么知道你们不是在骗我
How do I know you're not tricking me?
我们很可能在说谎
We probably are.
但万一我们没说谎呢
But what if we're not?
你们都觉得自己很机智对吧
You think you're so smart.
你们觉得我会再上一次当  对吧
You think I'm going to fall for it again, don't you?
我才不会
Well, I won't.
你要去哪
Where you going?
闭嘴
Shut up.
你真的不能去吗
Aw, are you sure you can't come?
我很想去  但我病得太严重了
I want to, but I'm just too sick.
可你真的很想见他
And you really wanted to meet him.
就是啊
I know.
我一直试着隐瞒病情好去见他
And I've been trying to hide it so I could go,
但我不想传染给他
but I don't want to make him sick.
是呢
Yeah.
你看起来确实挺苍白虚弱
Yeah, you do look pretty pale and clammy.
是啊
Yeah.
玩得开心
Have fun.
你快点好起来  好吗
Well, feel better, okay?
就只是我平常版的苍白病君子样啊
No, that's just my regular pale and clammy.
真的  最大的危机不是质量减少
I mean, really, the bigger danger isn't the loss of mass.
而是太阳会耗尽用作核燃料的氢
Instead, it will run out of hydrogen to use for nuclear fuel,
膨胀变成一个红巨星  把地球吞没
swell up into a red giant, and fry the Earth.
所以你不想分吃一份沙拉吗
So you don't want to split a salad?
不了  谢谢
No, thank you.
说到分开
But speaking of splitting things,
你听说过能提高光合作用效率的
did you hear about the light-splitting greenhouse film
分光温室棚膜吗
that could improve photosynthetic efficiency?
没有
No.
是我在给我制造的人类
Just a little something I read
喂奶时读到的小知识
while nursing a human being that I made.
我还是点鸡肉吧
I'm just gonna get the chicken.
"鸟又"  鸡反过来的写法
Ah. N-E-K-C-I-H-C: chicken backwards.
屌炸  妈妈大脑
Boom, mom brain.
再加一整瓶红酒
And a whole bottle of wine.
吃屎吧
In your face!
喂
Hello?
亲爱的  你感觉怎么样
Aw, hey, sweetie, how you feeling?
还行  我在休息
Okay. I'm just resting.
我有个惊喜也许能让你感觉好些
Well, I have a surprise that might make you feel better.
真的吗
Oh, really?
嗯  看这是谁呀
Yeah, look who's here.
等等  我认识你
Wait, I know you.
你不认识我
No, you don't.
我真的认识
Yes, I do.
你之前在我酒店楼下等我
You were waiting for me at my hotel.
你毁了我的领带
You ruined my tie.
等等  什么
Wait, what?
他在说什么
What's he talking about?
他很明显是在开玩笑啦
Uh, he, uh-- obviously, he's kidding.
这笑话真逗  比尔
That's a, that's a good one, Bill.
我先挂了
I got to go.
蠢人莱纳德
Stupid Leonard,
见蠢人比尔·盖茨
meeting stupid Bill Gates,
不带上蠢蠢的我
without stupid me.
对不起
对不起...谢尔顿
I am so sorry-- Sheldon?
莱纳德  我怎么忍心一直生你气
Oh, Leonard, I can't stay mad at you.
过来
Come here.
我接受你的道歉
Apology accepted.
晚饭吃什么  我快饿死了
What's for dinner? I'm starving.
"雷猴"
Hola.
又是这家伙
他哪根筋抽了
女士们好吗
How are you ladies doing?
"猴"就举一下手啊
Raise your hands if you're bueno.
谁会把孩子交给他照看啊
孩子可能是他偷来的
我系斯图尔特·布鲁姆呀
Me llamo Stuart Bloom.
快写下来
我们可能要报告给警察